My name is Miss Doris Ugbaji
I am from Benue State, Nigeria.
I am here to testify to the goodness of the Lord in my life.
I was delivered at The SCOAN from the spirit of woman, masturbation and pornography.
It all started when I was six years old.
My father used to bring some men into our house.
They would take me.
When I wanted to say, “Daddy, I don’t understand. What is this man here for?”,
he would say that I was a small child and didn’t know what I was doing.
I should keep quiet and see what he was going to do.
In the night, they would bring me out and use chicken to try and invoke some spirits into me.
We would go to a river, they would bathe me but I didn’t understand why.
When I was in primary school, I was brilliant and very intelligent but never knew what was happening.
When I got to school, they said they should take me to a boarding school.
I went to a boarding school, where I met a lady.
When I met the lady, she said she wanted me to be her friend.
I never knew that there was something attached or that she wanted to initiate me into anything.
On a fateful night, she called me to come to a corner because she had something to tell me.
I said, “OK, let’s go”.
At midnight, she woke me up and started touching me.
Something came over me and that was how I was initiated into the spirit of woman.
I started having affection for women.
She would touch me; I would touch her.
The next day, I came again.
We began to do it.
Whenever she saw me with another lady, she would begin to fight me,
asking why I was moving with the lady and what was happening.
I started having affection for women.
It affected my life in so many ways that even in class, I could not concentrate.
The next thing that would happen was she would come outside the window and give me a sign.
We would go to the dormitory.
I would say that I was not feeling fine or look for any excuse to go to the dormitory
so that me and her could have a good time.
From there, I started having affairs with many girls; I started dating women.
Wherever I went, if I saw them, I knew that this was the kind of spirit; we knew ourselves.
We didn't need to ask.
At times, I would be asked why I was moving with a girl and if there was anything we were doing.
I would say no and God forbid but it was a lie; inside me, I knew what I was doing.
When I came home, I pretended so that my mum would not know what was happening.
The next thing, I would be in my room.
Whenever I dreamt of a woman coming to me and making love to me, I would start masturbating.
OK.
So, you mean, apart from the physical meeting of this girl at school,
who initiated you into this practice of the spirit of woman,
you also used to have dreams of a woman coming to you.
Can you tell us more about that?
Yes, I used to have a dream.
A woman would come to me in a dream and whenever this woman came to me -
if I didn’t see any woman around to do it with, I would start masturbating.
I could masturbate in my room for two to three days; I would not come out.
I would not eat but I would be satisfied.
Whoever came to knock on my door, I would have the kind of anger that could kill somebody.
I would fight and say nobody should come to my door.
I would ask if they knew what I was doing in my room.
I was in a world of my own; I didn’t want anyone to advise me.
This spirit pushed me to be drinking and nobody knew that I was the kind of person who drank.
Because of how I looked, you would never know unless you caught me doing one thing or the other.
I started battling at school.
Before I finished my secondary school, I had to take the exam four times.
Nobody thought that I would go to a higher institution because
the kind of life that I was living was so dangerous.
So, you are someone that was very intelligent before this happened, right?
Yes.
But after this happened, all your grades, your study - you just put that idea out of your head, right?
Yes, I could not do anything in school.
Instead of me to concentrate, I would be looking for women to meet.
Wherever I met them, I would always be the man; they would be the woman.
When I managed to go to a higher institution, a lot of things happened to me but I managed to get through.
How did this spirit of woman also affect your relationships with men,
maybe boys were interested in having a relationship with you?
This spirit had affected me so much that I hated men; whenever I saw men, they irritated me.
I hated men; I didn’t like being around men.
When someone came to say they wanted to be my friend, I would say OK
but when they started dragging, I would hate them.
I didn’t have affection for men; I only had affection for women.
Even if I wasn’t doing anything with a woman, I preferred to be around women.
OK.
How did this affect you in your relationship with your family?
It had affected my relationship with my family in that there was no peace.
My mum, I hate--
If anybody should talk to me--
I would tell my dad that if he didn’t give me money, I would call armed robbers to come,
take it from him and give it to me.
I fought everybody.
I bought two jackknives so that nobody would talk to me or I would stab them.
They could not talk to me; there was no peace – everybody hated me.
My mum started saying that I was not the daughter she gave birth to;
something was wrong and it was not ordinary.
She told me to go The SCOAN; people were going there and I should too.
I said I didn’t want to come because I knew my spirit would be exposed
as I knew there were some spirits around me.
You knew right from that time that this was a spiritual problem?
Yes.
OK.
When you came here, during the mass prayer, tell us what was your experience?
During the mass prayer, I was there.
Before then, I met a youth and told him I didn’t understand my life,
I was facing a lot of challenges and didn’t know if I was coming or going.
The person said that I should go to mass prayer.
In my mind I said, “Which kind of mass prayer?”
I wanted to run away.
When I was trying to go, my legs became heavy and I could not go out.
I just managed to sit in one corner while they started the mass prayer.
That was where I was delivered from this spirit.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
We have many people in the auditorium today who have never experienced mass prayer before.
We want you to let us know; as the prayer was going on, what was your experience,
what was happening to you exactly? Describe that for us.
When I was about to go out, my whole body became hot.
I don’t know where the excess sweat coming out of my body came from.
I sat down while they were praying.
Then, I heard sounds like they were beating drums in my ears.
I was looking for a way out; I began to see darkness and felt heat all over my body.
I started vomiting and from there, I fell; I didn’t know what I was doing.
After the vomiting, we can see on the screen right now, the time that the evil spirit was manifesting in you.
Do you remember any of that?
No.
You don't remember that?
Praise God!
Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
Truly, that was deliverance in the power of the Holy Spirit.
After that experience, when you were delivered, tell us; what have been the changes you have seen?
To my own surprise, I found that after the deliverance, my phone which was like food to me
as I used to watch all kind of things on it, I wouldn’t sleep but now, I do not use my phone.
I feel it is like punishment to go online.
I started thinking straight that a woman should get married and have her own children.
I never thought there was something like that.
My mother would ask me, “You don’t want to get married; men are coming?”
I would think, “This old woman doesn’t even know what’s happening”.
I would not talk to her for a week; I would disappear from the house and go and meet my girlfriends.
Since then, the affection for women has gone?
Yes, everything has stopped.
I see women as my sisters; I don’t see them and think of dating anymore.
What about the dream you used to have of a woman coming to you in the night to torment you?
Yes, I used to dream about eating and different women coming to make love with me.
I don’t experience it anymore.
The only dream I have had was last night, I took a flight from where I was to The SCOAN.
I went to The SCOAN and landed. That was all.
Hallelujah, let's put our hands together for Jesus, the King of Glory!
With this deliverance you have experienced, we want you to advise viewers watching you all over the world,
and us, listening to you in the auditorium.
What is your word of advice?
My advice to viewers out there, especially young ladies and youth like me.
I know there are many people out there watching me.
I am not ashamed of anything; I am very happy to stand in the presence of God and giving this testimony.
There is nothing God cannot do.
The same God who delivered me will deliver those who have my problem.
There are a lot of them out there; I know how many I had been following.
Please, get ready for your deliverance and come to The SCOAN
because this was where I got my deliverance.
Hallelujah!
Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
That is a wonderful advice; when we have a problem, we should run to our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ,
we should run to any living church, of which The SCOAN is just one.
We believe that as you continue to make God's Word the standard for your life; better is not good enough -
the best is yet to come for you and your family, in Jesus' name!
Amen.